Preliminary Inventory to the Berton W. Crandall Photographs, 1888-1953
Hoover Institution Archives
Berton W. Crandall Photographs,
1888-1953
60022
Crandall, Berton W.
29 manuscript boxes (12 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Depicts Stanford University campus and buildings, Herbert Hoover, Lou Henry Hoover, the Hoover family, Leland Stanford, and Jane Lathrop Stanford.
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Provenance
This collection of photographs was given to the Hoover Institution Archives in 1960 by the photographer himself, Berton W. Crandall, from Palo Alto, California.
Access Points
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964--Pictorial works.; Hoover, Lou Henry, 1874-1944--Pictorial works.; Stanford, Jane Lathrop, 1828-1905--Pictorial works.; Stanford, Leland, 1824-1893--Pictorial works.; Stanford University--Pictorial works.; United States.
Introduction
The collection consists of two parts. Part 1 mainly documents the life and career of Herbert Hoover and his family, but also includes a few other interesting photographs. Part 2 contains photographs depicting the Stanford campus before the 1906 earthquake and damage resulting from the earthquake, as well as other general photographs. Materials in Part 2 are distinguished from those in part 1 by the "S" preceding each item number. Both parts consist of a variety of photographic formats, prints as well as nitrate, acetate, and glass plate negatives.
In each of the two parts, prints are housed first, with their corresponding negatives following. The negatives have been divided into four main categories:
1) "Safety" negatives (usually acetate). These were left in the archival boxes
2) Glass plate negatives. These were also left in the archival boxes but were placed in special folders and containers, with more rigid support
3) Nitrate negatives. These were placed in double sealed vapor proof envelopes in the freezer
4) Very badly deteriorating negatives. These were set aside for conservation evaluation
Container List
- Part 1. Photographs of Herbert Hoover and his family
  - Prints
    - Items 1 to 24 (Box 1.)
    - Items 25 to 51 (Box 2.)
    - Items 53 to 92 (Box 3.)
  - Negatives
    - Aacetate
      - Items 1 to 24 (Box 4.)
      - Items 54 to 69 (Box 5.)
      - Items 70 to 89 (Box 6.)
    - Glass plates-3 items (Box 7.)
    - Nitrate (Box 8.)
- Part 2. Photographs depicting the Stanford campus before the 1906 earthquake and damage resulting from the earthquake, as well as other general photographs
  - Prints
    - Items S-1 to S-170 (Box 9.)
    - Items S-171 to S-241 (Box 10.)
    - Items S-244 to S-309 (Box 11.)
    - Items S-310-6A to S-770 and miscellaneous prints (Box 12.)
  - Negatives
    - Glass plates
      - Size 8x10 (Box 13-17.)
      - Size 5x7 (Box 18-20.)
    - Acetate
      - Items S-1 to S-38 (Box 21.)
      - Items S-44-1 to S-124 (Box 22.)
      - Items S-125 to S-196 (Box 23.)
      - Items S-203 to S-264 (Box 24.)
      - Items S-265 to S-310-18 (Box 25.)
      - Items S-310-21 to S-609 (Box 26.)
    - Nitrate (Box 27.-28.)
    - In very bad condition (negatives stuck to glassine) (Box 29.)
Appendix: Description of Items
- PART 1
  - Herbert Hoover
    - Herbert Hoover as a baby, West Branch, Iowa (negative) (Item 1.)
    - Herbert Hoover at about 4 years old, sitting in a chair, West Branch, Iowa (negative) (Item 2.)
    - Herbert Hoover, Theodore Hoover, Mary (May) Hoover, Salem, Oregon, 1888 (negative and print) (Item 2a.)
    - Jesse Clark Hoover, father of Herbert Hoover (negative and 2 prints) (Item 2b.)
    - Herbert Hoover as a young man, standing (glass plate negative, negatives, and 3 prints, autographed) (Item 3.)
    - Herbert Hoover as a young man, hat on his lap, hands in his pockets (negative and print) (Item 3a.)
    - Faculty at Herbert Hoover's school, The Pacific Institute, Newburg, Oregon (print) (Item 3b.)
    - Herbert Hoover standing, coat open, vest showing, hands in his pockets, full face, 1899. Arnold Genthe portrait (2 negatives and 6 prints) (Item 4.)
    - Minthorn House in Newburg, Oregon (print) (Item 4a.)
    - Herbert Hoover with J. P. Mitchell and others standing by automobile, Perth? Australia, 1898 (2 negatives and 3 prints) (Item 5.)
    - Herbert Hoover bust, one view, three-quarter face, 1894. Published in Volume I of Memoirs, page 22, and identified as a student at Stanford University, 1891-1895 (3 prints) (Item 6.)
    - Herbert Hoover as a mining engineer in Perth, Australia, 1898 (2 negatives and 4 prints) (Item 6a.)
    - Herbert Hoover bust, three-quarter face, with glasses, as a sophomore at Stanford University, fall 1892 or spring 1893 (1 print) (Item 6b.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover shortly before their wedding (February 10, 1899), Monterey, California (print and negative) (Item 6c.)
    - Herbert Hoover, in dark overcoat and with a cap, standing with others next to car, Australia, 1903 (4 prints) (Item 6d.)
    - Herbert Hoover, seated, three-quarter face, one hand in pocket, one on knee. Published in World's Work Magazine, 1915 April (1 negative) (Item 7.)
    - Herbert Hoover standing, full face, holding dog by front paws (5 prints) (Item 8.)
    - Candidate Herbert Hoover with sons Herbert Hoover, Jr., and Allan Hoover, 1928 June 17. Taken in garden of "S" Street House, Washington, D.C. Underwood & Underwood (1 print) (Item 8a.)
    - Herbert Hoover, full face and shoulders. Photograph of Nuytten's etching, 1929 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 9.)
    - President Herbert Hoover, 1929-1933. Autographed photo by Fabian Bachrach (2 prints and copy negative) (Item 9a.)
    - Herbert Hoover, full face, head and shoulders. Photograph of Clarence R. Mattei's portrait, 1933 (2 negatives and 7 prints, including one autographed)) (Item 10.)
    - Herbert Hoover - Various poses with dog, 1935 September (7 negatives and 7 prints) (Item 11.)
    - Herbert Hoover bust, three-quarter face, 1940 September 3 (4 negatives) (Item 12.)
    - Herbert Hoover, seated on chair, full length, 1940 September 3 (1 negative) (Item 12a.)
    - Herbert Hoover bust, three-quarter face, hat on, holding pipe in hands away from face. Taken at the Bohemian Grove in 1947 by "Leon" (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 13.)
    - Herbert Hoover, waist up, hands showing. Photograph by Fabian Bachrach, 1948 (2 negatives and 2 prints) (Item 14.)
    - Herbert Hoover, full face, head and shoulders only. Photograph by Fabian Bachrach, 1948 (1 negative and 4 prints) (Item 15.)
    - Herbert Hoover's 77th birthday, 1951 August 10. AP News photograph of Herbert Hoover at his desk in the Hoover Institution, holding paper in hands. Presidential chair and flag (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 16.)
    - Herbert Hoover's 79th birthday, 1953 August 10. Seated in overstuffed chair with pipe in hands, book open on lap, vase in background, in N.Y. apartment? All the same pose but background either changed or retouched (3 negatives) (Item 17.)
    - Herbert Hoover, three-quarter face, head and shoulders, pipe in mouth and held by one hand, post presidential period (1 negative) (Item 18.)
    - Herbert Hoover, full face and shoulders, round collar. Underwood and Underwood, New York (1 negative) (Item 19.)
    - Herbert Hoover, full length, full face, hands in pockets, except for thumbs, round collar, London, 1914 (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 20.)
    - Herbert Hoover standing, with top hat on, probably in London on his way to Australia, 1897 April (1 negative and 3 prints) (Item 20a.)
    - Herbert Hoover sitting at table leaning forward slightly, hands clasped (1 negative) (Item 21a.)
    - Herbert Hoover sitting back in chair, three-quarter face, hands on arms of chair (1 negative) (Item 21b.)
    - Herbert Hoover and unidentified man, full length, full face, in hats and overcoats (1 negative) (Item 21c.)
    - Herbert Hoover sitting back in chair, hands on arms of chair, profile, with others in the room (1 negative) (Item 21d.)
    - Herbert Hoover standing outside of building (sign: Department of the Interior, National Park Service, Administration Building), with three men, full length, all holding hat in hand (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 22.)
    - Candidate Herbert Hoover with President Calvin Coolidge during the 1928 campaign (1 print) (Item 22a.)
    - Herbert Hoover. Fabian Bachrach portrait, n.d. (1 negative) (Item 23.)
    - Herbert Hoover and James Rolph? (1 print) (Item 23a.)
    - Herbert Hoover smoking pipe in basket chair at the Bohemian Club, 1939 October (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 23b.)
    - Herbert Hoover holding pipe in his hand (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 23c.)
    - Herbert Hoover at West Branch (1 print) (Item 23d.)
    - Herbert Hoover with King Albert and Queen Elizabeth of Belgium and unidentified man (possibly Mayor Rolph) on San Francisco-Oakland Ferry, 1919 October 14 (1 negative) (Item 23e.)
  - Lou Henry Hoover
    (see also 59g)
    - Lou Henry Hoover standing on grass before house in Tientsin, China, 1899-1902 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 24.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated in automobile, with woman standing on rear step and two men working on engine, 1903-1904 (1 negative) (Item 25.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover. Photograph of portrait of her in Red Cross uniform, knitting, WWI (1 negative) (Item 26.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover bust, three-quarter face, with large hat, London, 1914 (1 negative, 1 print) (Item 27.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover standing, full length, three-quarters left with head turned front, purse in hands, tiny print cotton dress with wide lace collar, silver chain, 1929-1933 (1 negative) (Item 28.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover bust, head in profile, facing left, turned somewhat front, dark dress with v-neckline, silver chain, slight smile, hair in knot at nape of neck, at the White House, 1932. Fabian Bachrach (2 negatives and 7 prints) (Item 29.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover bust, three-quarter face, dress as above, at the White House. Fabian Bachrach (1 negative) (Item 30.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated on couch in White House Oval Drawing Room, knitting, facing right, by the fireplace, dark dress, white collar and cuffs. Underwood and Underwood, 1928-1929 (1 negative) (Item 31.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover standing, full length, three-quarter left with face turned front, hair in band around head with bar pins, left hand holding the end of long chain with spaced balls, wearing long dress of metallic cloth, with train, draped, hanging sleeves, at the White House. Fabian Bachrach, 1932 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 32.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated at an exact replica of the desk at which President Monroe wrote the Monroe Doctrine, left profile, looking up, hands holding open book on desk. Harris and Ewing (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 33.)
    - Same as above, but looking down, writing. Harris and Ewing (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 33a.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in cotton dress for "Cotton Week," standing, right profile, fan in right hand at side, black velvet bow in hair, at White House party for British ambassador Mellon, 1932. Harris and Ewing (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 34.)
    - Same as above, but with Lou Henry Hoover seated, three-quarter left, looking down at the floor, fan in hands (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 35.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in cap and gown procession for honorary degree, Tufts College, Massachusetts, 1932 June 13 (1 negative) (Item 36.)
    - Close-up of 36 (1 negative) (Item 37.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, full length, with overcoat, left hand showing, smiling, with hat, 1936 March (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 38a.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, seated, with overcoat, hands clasped on lap, smiling, with hat, 1936 March (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 38b.)
    - Same as 38a but left hand not showing (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 38c.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, waist up, three-quarter front, hands clasped, with hat but without overcoat (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 38d.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, three-quarter length, hands clasped, slight smile, hat (1 negative) (Item 38e.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, waist up, no smile, hat, holding something in hands (1 negative) (Item 38f.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover talking to two Scout Board members, with Mrs. Rippin seated on the left (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 38g.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover eating lunch with Scout leaders, Girl Scout Camp, St. Louis, Missouri (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 38h.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover. Photographs of people, scenery, etc., taken on High Sierra camping trip, 1940 (64 negatives) (Item 39.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated in armchair, knitting, purse hanging over arm of chair, with small table and vase of flowers on it in background, 1940 September 3 (1 negative) (Item 40.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover riding a horse, arm outstretched, on High Sierra camping trip, 1940 (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 41.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated in rocking chair facing camera with grandchild Andrew (Andy) in lap (holding beads) and Allan, Jr., seated on couch next to chair, 1941 September (1 negative) (Item 42a.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated in rocking chair, holding grandchild Andrew (Andy) up with Allan, Jr., seated on couch next to chair, 1941 September (1 negative) (Item 42b.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated in rocking chair holding grandchild Andrew (Andy), who is playing with beads, and Allan, Jr., seated on couch next to chair, 1941 September (1 negative) (Item 42c.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover seated in chair, facing Allan, Jr. and holding Andrew (Andy) in her lap, who is chewing on her beads, 1941 September (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 42d.)
    - (1 enlarged negative of 42d) (Item 43.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover greeting Eagle Scout Hopkins at front door of her Stanford home, 1942 January 29 (2 negatives) (Item 44.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover. Photograph of Richard M. Brown's oil painting, 1949, which is a copy of DeLazlo's 1932 painting (see 49). Brown's painting is hanging in the Hoover Institution (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 45.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform leaning against a wall at her Stanford home, facing front, wearing hat (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 46.)
    - Same as above, but seated (1 print) (Item 46b.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, full length, standing on terrace of Stanford home, right profile, with hand on Wegie's neck (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 47.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover in Girl Scout uniform, no hat, seated face front, with one hand on Wegie's neck. At this time, Lou Henry Hoover was President of the Girl Scouts (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 48.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover bust. Photograph of DeLazlo's 1932 portrait (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 49.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover facing forward. Nickolas Murray of N.Y. (1 negative) (Item 50.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover, head only, three-quarter face. Fabian Bachrach (1 negative and 3 prints) (Item 51.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover and unidentified woman, 1916 (1 print) (Item 51a.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover holding her grandson, 1963 July 29. Underwood and Underwood (1 print) (Item 51b.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover standing, one arm around Wegie's neck (1 print) (Item 51c.)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Charles Delano Henry, mother and father of Lou Henry Hoover (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 51d.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover, 1893 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 51e.)
    - The Henry home in Monterey where Lou Henry and Herbert Hoover were married (1 print) (Item 51f.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover. Fabian Bachrach (4 prints of different poses) (Item 51g.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover. Photograph by Harris and Ewing, and photograph by Underwood and Underwood (2 prints) (Item 51h.)
  - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover (see also 6c and 88b)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover standing in garden of Stanford home, full length, Lou Henry Hoover with hands clasped, Herbert Hoover with hands in coat pockets, ca. 1940. B. W. C. photograph, which was used in Collier's Series, as well as a Christmas card inscribed "With Best Wishes" and signed by both (2 negatives and 2 prints) (Item 52.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover arriving in Palo Alto by automobile, 1928 November 5 (2 negatives and 2 prints) (Item 53.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover standing on terrace of their Stanford home, standing slightly apart from each other, Lou Henry Hoover holding hat in her hands, Herbert Hoover with arms at his side, 1928 (1 negative and 2 prints, including one with their son Allan?) (Item 54.)
    - Herbert Hoover, Lou Henry Hoover, Herbert Hoover, Jr., and Allan Hoover, West Branch, Iowa, during 1928 presidential campaign (1 print) (Item 54a.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover standing in garden of Stanford home, Lou Henry Hoover holding hat in hands with fringed shawl draped over arms, Herbert Hoover with hands by his side, pre-election period, 1928 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 55.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover sitting in wicker chairs in garden of Stanford home, Lou Henry Hoover leaning forward slightly with hands together on lap, Lou Henry Hoover holding large hat in one hand ("S" Street House?), 1928 (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 56.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover standing before front door of their Stanford home, Herbert Hoover with hands by his side, Lou Henry Hoover holding large hat in hands with fringed shawl draped over arm, 1928 (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 57.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover, off White House South Portico, 1932 June (1 negative and 2 prints) (Item 58a.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover standing before table loaded with flowers, Herbert Hoover with hands clasped, Lou Henry Hoover holding books and papers in hands, Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, New York City, 1933 February 12 (1 negative and 6 prints) (Item 58b.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover sitting on love seat, Lou Henry Hoover's hands together on lap, Herbert Hoover with one hand resting on knee; both with legs crossed, three-quarter face, facing to the right, not smiling, fall of 1932 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 59a.)
    - Same as 59a, but facing to the left (1 negative) (Item 59b.)
    - Same as 59a, but facing each other (1 negative and 3 prints) (Item 59c.)
    - Same as 59a, but smiling slightly (1 negative and 1 print)) (Item 59d.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover in Venice, 1913 (2 negatives and 2 prints, including one with Mr. and Mrs. Edgar Rickard) (Item 59e.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover on Florida trip, pre-presidential period, early 1929 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 59f.)
    - Lou Henry Hoover with fur piece. Portrait in oval frame (2 prints) (Item 59g.)
  - Hoover family (see also 8a, 54a, and 89g)
    - Hulda Minthorn Hoover (Herbert Hoover's mother). Portrait in oval frame (1 negative) (Item 60.)
    - Hoover family welcomed by neighbors to their Stanford home: President-elect Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover, Allan Hoover, Herbert Hoover, Jr. and his wife Margaret, as well as their two children, Herbert Hoover III (Pete) and Peggy Ann, 1928 November 5. Used for Christmas card (2 negatives and 4 prints) (Item 61.)
    - Hoover family welcomed back to Stanford University and to their Stanford home, 1932 November 8 (13 negatives and 13 prints) (Item 62a-m.)
    - Hoover family at Stanford home, Christmas 1933 (1 negative) (Item 63.)
    - Hoover family at Stanford home, Christmas 1939 (2 negatives-1 plain and 1 with signatures- and 1 print) (Item 64.)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Allan Hoover and children
    - Allan Hoover as a child, taken in woods, n.d. (glass plate negative) (Item 65.)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Allan Hoover and dog, 1937 (7 negatives) (Item 66.)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Allan Hoover, 1937 December 21 (9 negatives) (Item 67.)
    - Allan Hoover, Jr., as a baby, 1939 November (11 negatives) (Item 68.)
    - Mrs. Allan Hoover holding Allan Hoover, Jr., 1939 November (2 negatives) (Item 69.)
    - Andrew (Andy) Hoover, at one month, 1940 December (3 negatives) (Item 70.)
    - Allan Hoover, 1940 December (11 negatives) (Item 71.)
    - Allan Hoover, Jr., with dog, 1941 September (3 negatives) (Item 72.)
    - Andrew (Andy) Hoover, 1941 September (1 negative) (Item 73.)
    - Allan Hoover, Jr., and Andrew (Andy) Hoover, 1941 September (1 negative) (Item 74.)
    - Allan Hoover, Jr., by the fireplace, 1942 February (1 negative) (Item 75.)
    - Allan Hoover, Jr., and Andrew (Andy) riding a toy automobile and a rocking horse, 1942 February 19 (9 negatives) (Item 76.)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Theodore Hoover
    - Theodore Hoover, head and shoulders, 1935 October (2 negatives and 3 prints) (Item 77.)
    - Mrs. Theodore Hoover, head and shoulders, 1935 October (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 78.)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Edgar Rickard. Photograph of bust, 1928-1934 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 79.)
    - American Relief Administration - Miscellaneous scenes (18 negatives) (Item 80.)
    - Australia - Sons of Gwalia Mine, 1903 October 27 (2 negatives and 1 print) (Item 81.)
    - Australia - Kalgoorlie - "Camel Train," 1897 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 82.)
    - Hoover bookplate (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 83.)
    - Bust of Herbert Hoover by sculptor Thomas Gregory. Gift to the Hoover Institution by Mrs. Gregory in memory of her husband (3 negatives and 3 prints) (Item 84.)
    - Room occupied by the Hoovers during the Boxer Rebellion siege in China, with walls riddled with bullets (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 85.)
    - Machine guns and gun crew, Boxer Rebellion (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 86.)
    - Portrait of Li Hung-Chang, China (1 negative) (Item 87.)
    - City of Tientsin, China (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 88.)
    - Tientsin home (outside view). Prints in book by Anne Emery (1 print) (Item 88a.)
    - Herbert Hoover and Lou Henry Hoover with 5 others inside their Tientsin home (1 print) (Item 88b.)
    - Same as 85 (1 print) (Item 88c.)
    - Commission for Relief in Belgium - Miscellaneous activities (6 negatives and 2 prints) (Item 89a-f.)
    - Herbert Hoover, Lou Henry Hoover, Allan Hoover, and Herbert Hoover, Jr., on deck of the SS Olympia, 1918 October (1 print and 1 negative) (Item 89a.)
    - Dogs on Christmas card - "Wegie and Sons Bring Cordial Greetings from the Hoovers," n.d. (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 90.)
    - The Hoovers' house in London called "The Red House" (1 print) (Item 90a.)
    - Three dogs together, 1935 November (6 negatives) (Item 91.)
    - Girl Scout group at the Hoovers' Stanford home, 1934 December (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 92.)
    - Horses and sleds in Russia? (1 negative) (Item 93.)
    - Face of nine medals received by Herbert Hoover on 1938 European tour (2 negatives and 1 print) (Item 94.)
    - Herbert Hoover's Belgian passport, 1925 (1 negative) (Item 95.)
    - Herbert Hoover, Ignacy Paderewski, the Papal Nuncio (later Pope Pius XI) at the rededication of the Cathedral in Warsaw, Poland, 1919 (1 negative and 1 print) (Item 96.)
    - Proclamations to Herbert Hoover from the state of Arkansas and from the Mississippi Flood Relief (2 negatives) (Item 97.)
    - Interior cabin views at Rapidan Camp (2 negatives) (Item 98.)
    - Unidentified room with spool bookcase and framed portrait on top shelf (1 negative) (Item 99.)